

DAPHNE SMIT

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

CONTACT

- Louise Marie LoeberpIntsn 135 1062DD Amsterdam
- 0031 (0)6 30 80 55 51
- daphnesmit1986@gmail.com
- www.daphnesmit.nl

FOLLOW ME



LinkedIn

Github

LANGUAGE

DUTCH ENGLISH FRENCH



ABOUT ME

My Name Is Daphne Smit, a passionate Freelance Frontend Developer based in Amsterdam.

I am a Front-end Developer with an Interaction Design background and professional working experience since 2010.

I love and live digital. Coffee code repeat. I am a Big fan of open source and proud creator of: https://www.npmjs.com/package/use-cornify



WORKING EXPERIENCE

> DEPT AGENCY - FRONTEND DEVELOPER APRIL 2014 - MAR 2020

Dept is an international digital agency with offices around the world. Helping reinvent & accelerate their clients digital reality by creating experience s that people want and businesses need. www.deptagency.com From medior frontend developer I grew to a lead/principal position.

> ICEMOBILE - FRONTEND DEVELOPER

NOV 2013 - OCT 2014

IceMobile was founded in 2002 with the vision that mobile would become the most important medium in people's lives. I was responsible for creating The Bright Admin Console to manage saving digital stamps.

> MATTMO - FE DEVELOPER / INT.DESIGN

FEB 2010 - OCT 2013

Small design studio in the heart of Amsterdam



EDUCATION

> HOGESCHOOL VAN AMSTERDAM - BSC

2006 - 2010

Communication & Multimedia Design, Interactive Media

> UTRECHT UNIVERSITY

2004 - 2005

Information & Communication sciences



SKILLS

HTML/CSS/SCSS	• • • •	VUEJS	•	•	•	•	
REACTJS	• • • •	ANGULAR	•	•	•		
ES6/JAVASCRIPT	• • • •	TYPESCRIPT	•	•	•	•	•
NEXTJS	• • • •	WEBPACK, ETC	•	•	•	•	•
GIT	• • • • •	AZURE DEVOPS	•	•	•	•	•

DAPHNE **SMIT**

FRONTEND DEVELOPER



RECENT PROJECTS

> MIJN.MAANDAG.NL

2019 - 2020

Als je bij Maandag® werkt, verwachten we dat je elke maand je urenregistratie bij ons indient. Om dit zo makkelijk mogelijk te maken hebben we zelf Mijn Maandag® ontwikkelt. In deze portal registreer je snel je uren én zakelijke kilometers.

Build on: NextJS, React + Hooks, Styled Components, Styled System, Docz, Azure Devops: Pipelines, Artifacts.

Role: Lead

> ZAKELIJK.MAANDAG.NL

2019 - 2020

Portal voor Maandag Opdrachtgevers om uren goed te keuren, vacatures te plaatsen en hun professionals van Maandag te beheren.

Build on: NextJS, React + Hooks, Styled Components, Styled System, Docz, Azure Devops: Pipelines, Artifacts.

Role: Lead

> BUGABOO.COM

2019

Bugaboo B2C webshop in Salesforce Commerce Cloud. In 4 months time we developed and launched their new webshop in 26 countries and 14 languages.

Build on: Salesforce Commerce Cloud, ES6/Vanilla JS, SCSS, Webpack.

Role: Lead

> GALL.NL 2018 - 2019

Gall & Gall is dé drankspecialist sinds 1884. Koop je wijn, whisky, champagne, bier of sterke drank eenvoudig online. Voor 22:00 besteld, morgen in huis!

Build on: Salesforce Commerce Cloud, ES6/Vanilla JS, SCSS, Webpack.

Role: Lead

> ETOS.NL 2018 - 2019

Etos is the biggest drugstore of the Benelux. Together with the team we created the Etos webshop!

Build on: Salesforce Commerce Cloud, ES6/Vanilla JS, SCSS, Webpack.

Role: Lead

> OTHER PROJECTS

< 2018

Brenntag Connect - Brenntag Chemicals **Build on**: Custom Express Server, Custom SSR, React, Emotion. https://brenntagconnect.com/

Toon.nl - Eneco

Build on: Custom Express Server, Custom SSR, React, Emotion.

bakertillyberk.nl - Baker Tilly Berk **Build on:** Angular|S, SCSS.

CONTACT



Q 0031 (0)6 30 80 55 51

🔀 daphnesmit1986@gmail.com

www.daphnesmit.nl